往昔
牧師Boyle帶領你走向光輝時刻
Reverend Buddy Boyle Going For Glowing Hour
當天使降臨
When angels come and knock in
奉獻出的你軀殼吧
Let them all in
沒有人類的許可 天使是無法附身的對吧
Angels can't possess a human without permission,right
沒錯
Yep
所以天使們用這傢伙寸照容器嗎
So,what?They're using this guy to find vessels
有一大堆心甘情願的觀眾啊
It's a willing audiance
是誰讓Crowley掌握大權的
Who put Crowley in charge
他可是我們的王
He's the King
他只是個商人
He's a salesman
現在
Right now
咱們來談談更朝換代
You and I have to talk about the regime change
你是我們的了
You're ours
你這個混蛋惡魔
Your demon ass
馬上就要變成個混蛋人類了
Is going to be a mortal ass
一眨眼的事兒
It'll be damn quick
我要怎樣
Where do I start
才能求得寬恕
To even look for forgiveness
不如從這個開始
How about we start with this
你變成凡人了嗎
You're human
Zeke
Castiel不能留在這兒
Castiel cannot stay here
他會把天使們都引到這裏的
He'll bring the angels down to all of us
他能避開天使
He's warded
但他還是被April找到了
He was warded when April found him
Castiel有危險
Castiel is in danger
如果他在這兒
And if he's here
我就有危險
I am in danger
等等 你怎麼會有危險
Wait,you're in danger
如果他留下
If he stays
恐怕我就只能離開了
I'm afraid I'll have no choice but to leave
Cass 咱們需要談一談
Cass can we talk
你不能留在這兒
You can't stay
雷克斯福德 愛達荷州
先生 先生 你在聽嗎
Sir,sir can you hear me
麻煩您說點兒什麼
Please,please just say something
你還在嗎
Are you still there
隨便說點兒什麼 我可以幫你
Keep talking and I can help you through this
求你了 先生 如果你還在聽
Please,sir,if you can hear me
請別掛斷電話
Stay on the phone
你現在可能很絕望 但是
It may feel hopeless right now but
你打這個熱線是有原因的
But you call the hotline for a reason
在你內心深處 還是有求生慾望的
There's some part of you that still want to live
還是知道自殺
Some parts that know suicide
你是誰
Who are you
是熱線電話裏那位女士叫你來的嗎
Did the lady from the hotline send you
不
No
是你叫我來的
You did
來擊個掌
High five
早啊 Steve
Morning,Steve
快遞
Mail
擊 個掌
High five
抱歉 我來晚了
Sorry,I'm late
我得把孩子送到育兒所
I had to drop the baby off at the daycare
一路上淨是紅燈
Then hit every red lights on the way here but
看來我不需要擔心什麼
Guess I should've worried
店面看起來不錯
Place looks great
咖啡杯
Coffee urns
滿的
Full
牛奶呢
Dairy case
都裝好了
Stocked
好吧
Okay
最後一個問題
Steve,last questions
從前你都去哪兒了
Where have you been all my life
你跟其他的銷售助理不大一樣
You're not like the other sales associates
你有些 不一樣的地方
There's something different about you
我能保證我沒有
I can assure you there's not
我懂
I know these things
你
You're
你很特別
You're special
你的大好消息就是
That's your big news is that
把預言石翻譯成了塗鴉嗎
You translated the tablets into doodles
是楔形文字
It's Cuneiform
我沒辦法直接把預言石翻譯成英語
I hit a wall translating the tablet into English
但是我發現了一本古老的手抄本
But I find an ancient codex
能把天使文翻譯成
Linking the angel script to
古埃蘭楔形文字
Proto-Elamite Cuneiform and
於是我就能把預言石板和筆記
I was able to translate the tablets and the footnotes
都翻譯成古埃蘭文 但是它們
Into Elamite which is
是塗鴉
Doodles
早就滅絕了
It's extinct
你能認出這些字嗎
Can you read it
沒人能
No one cans
學者們已經研究好幾個世紀了
Scholars have tried for centuries
所以 這是個死胡同
So,it's an dead end
不完全是
And not quite
大多數古埃蘭文字都是抽像的
Now,most Proto-Elamite is abstract
但我從Metatron的筆記裏
But I was able to decipher one phrase
認出了一個詞
From Metatron's footnotes
墜落的天使
Falling angels
這麼說
Okay,so
那些筆記涉及到了Metatron的咒語
The footnotes refer to Metatron's spell
有可能
Maybe
好吧
Okay
要是我們能翻譯出筆記
Well,maybe if we can decipher the footnotes
也許就能逆轉咒語
Then we can reverse the spell
讓那幫長翅膀的混蛋滾回天堂
Punt those wingy dicks back to Heaven
從哪兒入手
Where do we start
查資料
Research
泡泡圖書館
Comb through the library
看看能不能找到埃蘭文的資料
See if you can find anything else on Elamite
Zimmerman滅絕語言大百科
Zimmerman's Encyclopedia of Extinct Languages
第一卷 Adai到Adakapa
Volume 1:Adai to Adakapa
這玩意兒一共多少卷
How many volumes are there
24卷
別擔心 一卷都沒丟
Don't worry,we've got them all
太棒了
Awesome
太及時了
There's a God
喂
Hello
我這兒有個案子
I may have a case for you
愛達荷州 雷克斯福德市
Four were missing in Rexford Idaho
有四例失蹤人口 疑似死亡
Presumed dead,you know
屍體很奇特
Body's been released a lovelies
而且案發現場
And there were reports of
還發現了一種奇怪的物質
A strange substance at the scenes
我也很高興聯繫上你 Cass
Well,hello to you,too Cass
你最近怎麼樣
How are you
我 很忙
I am busy
好吧 那你想怎麼入手調查
All right,so how do you want to do this
跟你在現場見 還是我去接你
Want to meet you at the latest scene or want me to pick you up
我現在很忙
I've got my hands full over here
我只是
I just
Cass 你還在嗎
Cass,hello
覺得你想瞭解一下案情
Thought you'd want to know about the case
嘿 你確定一切都正
Hey,you sure everything is
常嗎
Kay
他沒說自己在哪兒
So he said nothing about where he is
也沒提他都幹了什麼是嗎
Or what he's been doing
這可是Cass
This is Cass
他可從來都不擅長聊天
In case you forgot he's not exactly chatty Cathy
你也不準備在愛達荷州去見見他嗎
And you're not even gonna see him when you're in Idaho
我說過了 只要天使看見他就像貓看見貓薄荷一樣
Like I said,as long as he's on his catnip for angels
他就要刻意跟咱們保持距離
He's keeping a distance
所以
So
這一切有什麼意義嗎 Dean
Then what's the point,Dean
這都不算我們管的案子啊
I mean,it's barely even case
所以我這就上路 去看看他怎麼樣
That's why I'm gonna go and have a little look see
我才不會把所有精力都浪費在
And I'm not gonna waste the whole of the menpower
一堆沒用的破爛上
On a big pile of nada
你就是找借口
In other words,a perfect excuse
不想查資料
To bail out on research
被你發現了
You got me
嘿 Steve
Hey,Steve
我在儲物櫃裏發現了這個
I found this in the supply closet
你知道這是誰的嗎
Do you know whose it is
是我的
That's mine
謝謝
Thanks
我還在儲物格子了發現了一卷睡袋
I also found a roll of sleeping bag on the tool locker
是的 我想仔細把存貨清單都查一遍
Yes I wanted to be thourough with inventory so
所以上週末加班有點兒晚
I worked late last weekend
在這兒睡上一覺
Taking a nap here was easier than
比回家在床上睡方便多了
Going back home to my bed
當然 我有床 也有家
Which I have,of course,a bed in home
Steve 你真是太負責任了
Steve,you're so responsible
我一直沒好意思問
I've been afraid to ask
我不想仗著你是我員工就佔你便宜
I don't want to take advantage of you as my employee
我也不想破壞
And I certainly don't want to jeopardize
咱們的同事關係
Our working relationship
但是作為一個單親媽媽
But as a working single mom,it's
約會是一件可遇不可求的事情
Hard enough to get a date
我碰上了一個這麼好的男人
Let alone meet a really great guy
明天晚上我休假
Tomorrow is my night off
我知道你也休假
And I know you're off too
所以我在想有沒有可能
And I was just wondering if there's any chance
明晚你有時間嗎
That you're free tomorrow night
當然有
Yes
非常有
你真好
You're the best
所以 有四個人失蹤
So,four missing
四個都死了
Four dead
死亡已經證實了
Just got confirmation
四個受害者有什麼共同的敵人嗎
And any common threat you can think of
Joe的速撥通訊錄上有自殺開導熱線
Joe in there had a suicide hot line on speed dial
上一個失蹤的女孩
And the gal before him
生病在家 抽屜裏收集的抗憂鬱藥
Was a shut-in who had enough anti-depressants
多得能開藥店了
In her medicion cabinet to stock a pharmacy
一號受害者
First victims
是蘇格市的一對夫妻
Maried a couple out of sugar city
以和諧離婚而出名
Pretty much a walking billboard for no fault divorce
他們生活上都不是很順心嗎
Were they all basket cases
如果你讓我列出
If you ask me to make a list
本地最悲觀的人
Of this county saddest sacks
他們四個絕對是打頭的
These four will be right on the top
好吧 四個不開心的受害人
All right,so four unhappy people
其中一個有自殺傾向
One of them definitely suicidal
但是你已經排除自殺了
But you've ruled out suicide
你會需要它們的
You are goona want to put these on
這看起來像是自殺嗎
This look like suicide to you
血跡嗎
Blood
如果實驗結果跟其他前幾個一樣的話
If the tests come back same as the others
這是所有東西
It's everything
血液 皮膚 毛髮 指甲 內臟
Blood,skin,hair,nails internal organs
甚至還有衣料
Even clothing fibres
就像他們自己鑽進了
Like these poor souls,got run to the
世界上最好的碎木機一樣
World's finest wood-chipper
有沒有目擊者
What about witnesses
跟其他案件一樣
Same as the rest
鄰居們說有什麼 一陣粉紅色的光
Neighbors reported some kind of a pink flash
我們到這兒的時候
By the time we got here
這就是所有剩下的東西了
All that was left was this
我們基本都查過了
Yeah,we're almost through texts over here
什麼都沒發現
We got nothing
也許你應該試試打給Morrison教授
Maybe try professor Morrison
我們聯繫不上他
Yeah,he's unreachable
他休假了 去新幾內亞
He took a sabbatical to live amongst
愉快地玩耍了
The Trobrianders of Papus New Guinea
我們現在陷入了僵局
Needless to say,we are pretty burned
還有一個人
Well,there's one guy there
每天都沒事幹
Who's nothing notify-rested
你是說Crowley嗎
Crowley
我就是說說
I'm just saying
把他綁著又不是為了好玩兒
We're not keeping him chained up for the one liners
值得一試
That's worth a shot I guess
小心行事
Just be careful all right
別被他的小伎倆耍了
Don't fall for his quid pro quo crap
知道了
Noted
你怎麼樣
So what about you
Cass給的線索有什麼進展嗎
How's Cass's lead panning out
四個受害人 突然爆炸至死
Four victims suddenly exploded
我測過電磁場
Now I've tried the EMF
也找過巫術袋或者硫磺
I've looked for the hex bag,sulfer
什麼都沒有
Nada
人體自燃嗎
Spontaneous combustion
圖勒人幹的嗎
Maybe the Thules
不不
No,no
我已經把它們排除了
I already ruled them out
屍體是蒸發了 不是燒燬了
The bodies were vaporised,weren't burned
聽起來是我們管的案子
That sounds like a real case
Dean 我應該跟你一起
Dean,I should be there
不了 沒有必要
No,man,that's not nessacary
不用了 我
No,I
我自己能搞定
I got this one covered
他甩了我 Jace
He dumped me,Jace
在食堂裏
In the cafeteria
當著所有人的面
In front of everyone
實在是 誰會這麼做啊
It's just like,who does that,you know
為什麼不能在Facebook上把我甩了呢
Why can't he just dump me on facebook
像個正常人那樣
Like a normal person
我完蛋了
I've been destroyed
無論是社交上還是情感上
Socially and romantically
完全的失敗者
Totaled
我想鑽地洞了 Jace
Just so embarrassed,Jace
都有心去死了
I'd just die
我可以幫你
I can help with that
什麼
What
謝謝
Thanks
祝您愉快 女士
Good day,ma'am
還有 祝您好運
And good luck
我要一包牛肉乾 還有薄荷糖
I'll have some beef jerky and a pack of menthols
你在這兒幹什麼
What are you doing here
見到你我也很高興 Cass
Jeeze,nice to see you too,Cass
我現在叫Steve
It's Steve,now
見到你我很驚訝
And you surprised me
不瞞你說 我也很驚訝
Well,the feeling is mutual
我知道我們要低調
Man,we had to lay low for the angel threat
但是 哇哦 你這掩護身份真成功
But...Whoa,this is some cover
我沒有榮光了 你覺得會怎麼樣
My grace's gone.What did you expect
你知不知道
Do you have any idea how hard it was
我墜天的時候有多難 我不僅僅是丟了榮光
When I fell to earth,I didn't just lose my powers
我
I
我一無是處了
I am nothing
現在
Now
我是銷售助理
I'm a sales associate
-銷售助理啊 -嘿Steve
-Sales associate -Hey,Steve
在這兒簽下字
You sign here
我負責存貨
I'm responsible for inventory
出售 還有客戶服務
Sales,customer service
我讓這裏 謝謝
I keep this place...Thank you
保持乾淨整潔的狀態
Clean and presentable and
經理忙的時候
When my manager's busy
我還會準備吃的
I even prepare the food
哇 你從
Whoa,so you went from
天堂裏的戰士
Fighting heavenly battles
變成專門加熱肉卷的了
To nuking taquitos
還有墨西哥玉米片
Nachos,too
我這幾周來 都在
I've been politely asking
很友好的請你送幾本好書下來
To reading material for weeks
你就給我拿來這個啊
This is what you bring me
-我不看 -你到底懂不懂古埃蘭語
-Pass -Can you read Elamite or not
那是我最喜歡的古語
It's by no means,my favourite of the ancient tongues
-我是懂 -能幫我們破解嗎
-But yes -Will you help us read it
我為什麼要幫你
Why on earth would I
因為那晚我也在
Because I was there,that night
我看到你的人性
I saw what humanity did to you
不管你喜不喜歡 你心中的某一部分
Like it or not,there's still a little
不是混蛋
Part of you that's not a douche
抱歉了 麋鹿 我是個徹頭徹尾的混蛋
Sorry moose,to the last drop
Crowley 你活下來的唯一原因
Crowley,the only reason you're alive
是因為我哥覺得你有用
Is my brother thought you'd be useful
目前為止 你什麼用都沒有
So far you've done Jack
看來我們要考慮備用計劃了
Back to Plan B I guess
什麼備用計劃
Which is
把你送給Abaddon
Give you up to Abaddon
你以為用那個小賤人就能威脅到我
You think you can threaten me with that hack
她被憤怒沖暈了頭 沒有一點兒用處
She's all fury,no finesse
我還真不確定
I'm not so sure
上次我們見她的時候 她
Our last encounter with Abaddon,she was
她挺嚇人的
She's pretty terrifying
比你嚇人多了
Scarier than you've been in years
紙給我
Bring that to me
這不是你
This is not you,man
你可是個天使啊 別鬧了
You're above this.Come on
不 Dean 我不是
No,Dean.I'm not
我沒能做好一個天使
I failed to be an angel
我想做好事 但每次結局都不對
Everything I ever attempted came out wrong
在這兒
But here
至少我還有做對的機會
At least I have a shot to getting things right
我猜你可能看不到 但是
I guess you can't see it,but
我的工作中有尊嚴存在
There's a real dignity in what I do
人類的尊嚴
A human dignity
我不想打擾你們 但是有個顧客
Hate to interrupt you guys,but a customer
在男廁裏出了點兒小問題
Had an accident in the men's room
我就去
I'm on it
哦對了 今晚
Oh,and tonight
你7點過來 沒問題吧
7 at my place work for you
沒問題
Great
你真好
You're the best
這才是真正原因
That's what this is about
什麼
What
-那個姑娘 -不是的 Dean
-The girl -No,Dean
不是
It's not
Nora
她人很好
She's a very nice woman
我非常確定 她不想取我性命
I'm pretty she's not a reaper intend on killing me
她還約我出去
And she's asked me out
人類是會去約會的 對吧
Going on dates,something humans do,right
我一般碰不上單身就不約會
My dates usually end when I run out of singles
對 對 我們都是
But,yeah,yeah,that's something
會 去 約會的
That...humans...do
我是Lee Ermey探員
This is Agent Lee Ermey
我馬上就過去
I'll be right there
又一起兇殺案 在一所高中裏
This is another kill,over at the high school
你來嗎
You coming
我都沒有榮光了 去了有什麼用
I won't be much use,I don't have my powers
所以呢 我從來都沒有過
So?I've never had powers
你是獵人
You are a hunter
你是獵人學徒 記得嗎
And you're a hunter-in-training,remember
是 我記得
Yeah,I remember
-你說我很差勁 -我沒說過
-You said I sucked -I didn't say that
我只是說
I said there was a
有進步的空間 來吧
You know,a room for improvement.Come on
好吧 我還有5分鐘下班
All right.My shift's over in 5 minutes
-約會是在晚些時候 -這就對了
-My date's not until later -Attaboy
我去開車
I'll go to get the car
別急
Not just yet
我先把衛生間清理了
I have to clean the bathroom
我們本來在說話
One second,we're talking
然後她突然
And the next,she just
沒有動靜了 之後
Stops and then
整個食堂裏的人都嚇呆了
Everyone in the cafeteria,freaks
大家衝到窗戶前 指著窗外
Rushing and pointing out window at
天啊 真的是她嗎
God,could that really be her
沒有人看到其他陌生人出現嗎
And nobody saw anybody else at the scene
不管是男的還是女的 沒有不尋常的地方嗎
A man or a woman...anything unusual
你的朋友 有抑鬱的跡像嗎
Your friend,was she...depressed
-什麼意思 -有自殺傾向嗎
-Depressed? -Any thoughts of suicide
沒有
No
她可能有有些不高興
I mean she's kind of bummed that dick bag Travis
她的混蛋前男友當著全校的面甩了他
Broke up with her in front of whole school
-有些不高興 -對
-Kind of bummed -Yeah
比她考試拿C要不高興得多
Like more bummed than she got a C on a quiz and
但沒有她父母離婚時那麼沮喪
Less bummed than when her parents split up
就是 不高興
Kinda...bummed
失陪
Excuse me
Cass 怎麼了
Cass?What's wrong
我以前見過
I've seen this before
什麼 在哪兒見過
What?Where
在天堂
In heaven
什麼意思 是天使干的嗎
What,you're saying an angel did this
不是普通天使
It's no ordinary angel
Dean 這次太糟了
Dean,this is bad
非常嚴重
This is very bad
在天堂裏
On the battlefields...of heaven
有一級特殊的天使
There was a special class of angel
叫Rit Zien
The Rit Zien
天使語中的救濟天使
Enochian for hands of mercy
他們就像醫護人員 上戰場
They function like medics.They tended to the wounded
去救受傷的天使 特別是很難好的傷 但是
They healed those who couldn't be healed,but
對於那種救不回來的重大創傷
For the mortally wounded those who were
Rit Zien的任務就是毀滅
Past saving,the rit zien's job was to put them down
就是炸成碎片嗎
But the granulated bodies
這是他們的特殊能力
This was their...special ability
他們這種毀滅的能力
They had this way of smiting that was so
很快 很徹底
Quick and so total that it rendered
甚至都不會有疼痛感
Death virtually painless
但是他們下手的對象不是受傷的天使
But these aren't wounded angels
他們都是普通人類
That they are vaporizing.They are people
你說得對
Right
我也不知道
I don't know
Rit Zien尾隨痛苦而來
The Rit Zien home in on pain
痛苦就像是他們的燈塔
It's like a beacon to them
所以 當此天使墜天以後
So,when this angel fell to earth
他肯定聽到了受害人的痛苦
He heard the victim's cries,their anguish
就像在天堂能聽到天使的痛苦一樣
Same to hear the angel in heaven
他在人間繼續曾經在天堂的工作
He's continuing his heavenly work down here
每次一個受難的凡人
One suffering human at a time
嗯 但是這個女孩兒沒有受苦受難
Yeah,but this last victim was not suffering
就只是一個衝動的孩子而已
Just a normal moody kid
但是他剛才來過了
But he just got here
人類情緒的變幻莫測
The ebb and float human emotion
Dean 我也來凡間好幾年了
Dean...I've been on earth for a few years
我才剛剛能理解 對他來說
And I've only begun to grasp,to him
痛苦不會消失
Pain is pain
那麼所有人都有可能是下一個受害者了
So everybody is fair game
真好 我們得阻止他
All right,well,we got to stop him
你要阻止他
You have to stop him
你害怕了
You're scared
現在不一樣了 Dean
It's different now,Dean
一切都不一樣了
Everything feels different
說得對
You're right
好吧 那我去追這位
All right,I'll track down this
變態醫生 再幹掉他
Kevorkian wanna be,and I'll put him down
好
Okay
你別惹麻煩
You stay safe
去約會
Go on that date,all right
過正常人的日子
G live a normal life
好
Okay
還有事嗎
Well
我需要你載我一程
I need a ride
好吧
Right
我答應你
I'll do it
但是不是無償的
But I want something in return
-你要什麼 -打一通電話
-What's that -A telephone call
別這樣 麋鹿
Come on,moose
就算是Dahmer也有打電話的權利
Even Dahmer got one telephone call
注 Jeffery Dahmer是美國20世紀時一位連環殺人案件真兇
你真想
Seriously
讓他給Abaddon打電話嗎
You wanna let Crowley communicate with Abaddon
一個地獄之王加上企圖篡權的地獄騎士
A king and a power-mad knight of hell isn't enough
你還嫌不夠亂 想組個混種惡魔軍團是嗎
You wanna throw a demonic team up into mix
我不這麼想
I don't think so
我是說 我也不相信Crowley 但是
I mean...I don't trust Crowley either,but
說實話 我覺得他不會和Abaddon合作
I can't honestly see him working with Abaddon
他恨死她了
He hates her too much
你自己說的
You said it
你不相信他
You can't trust him
我們不一定要相信
We don't have to
Crowley已經被困住了
Look,Crowley's bound
我們可以隨時掛電話
We can end the call whenever we want
就算他想給Abaddon洩露什麼消息
Even if he wanted to give Abaddon information
他也沒什麼好透露的
He has nothing to give her
他連基地的位置都不知道
He don't even know where the bunker is
他說他能破解那些文字
He says he can decrypt the translation
他要是撒謊怎麼辦
What if he's lying
這倒是
You're right
我們需要證據
We'll need proof
這些怎麼解
What are these
-材料 -什麼材料
-Ingredients -More specific
一個 咒語的材料
Ingredients...for a spell
拿非利人的心 丘比特的弓
Heart of a Nephilim,Cupid's bow
天使的榮光
Grace of an angel
剩下的呢
And the rest of them
電話
Phone call
等我打了電話 就告訴你們剩下的
You'll get the rest,when I get paid
現在 你們誰願意
Now,who's gonna be a dear
把電話給我啊
And open up a vein
到了
Okay
謝謝你 Dean
Thanks Dean
Cass 等一下
Cass,wait
我不能就這麼讓你進去
I can't let you do this
什麼
What
你就穿這個
You're gonna wear that
去約會嗎
On a date
我只有這一身
This is all I have,Dean
好吧
Okay
馬甲脫了
Lose the vest
-為什麼要 -脫馬甲 快
-What do you -Lose the vest,come on
這樣稍微好一點兒了
That's a little better.All right
這樣才對
There we go.All right
解扣子
And now your button
解開幾個口子
Why don't you unbutton it
好
Okay
等等等 夠了夠了
That's...that's far enough
Tony Manero
注 Tony Manero是歌舞片週末夜狂熱中的男主角
好了 你看起來不錯
Yeah,good,all right
聽我說 一定要你給她開門
Listen to me,always open the door for her,okay
一定要問好多問題
Ask a lot of questions
女人們就喜歡這個
They like that
如果她說她想去荷蘭
And if she says she's happy to go Dutch
她一定在撒謊
She's lying
好了
All right
去吧 帥哥
Go and get her,tiger
不錯嘛
Nice touch
你怎麼倒車呢 混蛋
What are you doing,jackass
喂
Hey
Steve 你能來真是太好了
Steve,I'm so glad you're here
進來吧
Come in
我以為我會趕不上呢
I thought I was gonna be late
-趕不上什麼 -我的約會
-Late for what -My date
我要去打保齡球 太難以置信了吧
Bowling,would you believe it
不過就算是去打保齡球
But,damn if I'm not dressing fancy
我也要盛裝
Even for bowling
自從Tanya出生以來 我都一直沒機會穿
Haven't had an excuse to doll up since Tanya was born
來看看我的小天使
There she is,my little angel
我已經餵過她了
Now she's already been fed
我估計她會一直睡下去
She'll probably sleep the whole time
反正我只出去幾個小時
And I'll only be gone for a couple of hours
我平時用的保姆過不來
I just couldn't get my usual sitter and
萬一她醒過來哭泣的話
I need somebody here in case
我需要有人在家看著她
She wakes up and starts crying
不過我保證她不會的
Which she won't,I promise
Tanya從來不哭
Baby Tanya never cries
祝我好運吧
Wish me luck
還有謝謝你 你真是個好人
And thank you,you really are the best
看孩子啊
Babysitting
不行 不行
A-bup-bup
怎麼了
What
不要你的 要他的
Not yours,his
這有什麼區別嗎
What difference does it make
我用過你的了
I've had yours
我都已經被困在這兒了
Stuck in here
在飲食上要求點兒花樣不算過分吧
Can't fault me for wanting a little variety
不可能
No way
怎麼了 小朋友
What's wrong,short round
難道你害怕針頭嗎
Afraid of needles
不 只是我個人的原則是
No,I just have policy not giving blood
不給殺了我母親的人提供血液
To anyone who's murdered my mother
我有的是時間
I have nothing but time
你個混蛋
You're a dick
祝你們翻譯順利
Good luck with that translation
咒語
Spells
我是Crowley
This is Crowley
幫我接 是Crowley
Connect me to...Crowley
信號不大好
Bad connection
Crowley 你們的王
Crowley,your king
如果你現在不給我接Abaddon
If you don't connect me to Abaddon right away
我就不得不
I'll be forced to
怎麼了 發生什麼了
What,what happened
他們讓我等一下
I've been placed on hold
你好
Hello
呃
Um
別 別哭
Please,please don't
好吧 好吧
Okay,okay,
我給你唱個搖籃曲吧
How about a lullaby
好了 噓 噓
Okay,shh,shh
看看我身上都發生了什麼
Look at what's happening to me
連我自己都不敢相信
I can't believe it myself
忽然之間我坐在雲端
Suddenly I'm on top of the world
忽然之間又變成了普通人
Suddenly I'm somebody else
哦 不管你信不信
Oh,believe it or not
我現在感覺很開心
I'm walking on air
我從沒想過自己會如此自由
I never thought I would be so free
支起翅膀飛向遠方 一路歌唱
Flying away on a wing and a prayer
哦 那人會是誰
Oh,who could it be
不管你信不信
Believe it or not
這就是我
It's just me
不管你信不信
Believe it or not
這就是我
It's just me
我就知道
I know,I know
探長
Sheriff
有個好消息
Here's a wrinkle
第一個犯罪現場 那對夫婦的死亡現場
Our first crime scene,married couple
我們剛從實驗室那邊獲得了化驗結果
Full analysis of the spray just came from the lab
現場只有那妻子的DNA
Turns out it only contains the wife's DNA
那就是說那丈夫還活著
The husband's still out there
沒人告訴過你
Nobody told you
也沒人解釋過
Nobody explained
你就這麼
You just shoved out
連哭帶喊的誕生在這世界裏
Kicking and screaming into this human life without
也不知道為什麼你會感覺到你所感覺的一切
Any idea why any of you feels the way you feel
也不知道為什麼會有那麼多困惑
Or why this confusion
感覺就像是
It just feels like it's a hair's breadth from
恐懼 或者痛苦
Terror,or pain
就當你以為你明白一切了的時候
You know,just when you think you do understand
結果發現你還是什麼都不懂
It'll turned out you were wrong
你什麼也不明白
You didn't understand anything at all
事實就是這樣的
This is just how it is when you're new at this
其實就在不久之前
You know,it wasn't that long ago
我只要輕觸一下你的額頭
All I need to do to ease your pain is
就會解除你的痛苦
Is touch you
你的溫度有點高啊
You're very warm
這正常嗎
Is that normal
噓 噓
Shh,shh
他差點兒就精神失常了
He's already a bit screwy
但他又找到了信仰
But then he found religion
她是個絕對的無神論者
She was a hard line atheist no peach herself
當他對那個愚蠢的Boyle牧師表現出極大的興趣後
When he got himself obsessed with this Buddy Boyle wackjob
本來就很糟的婚姻變得愈發不可收拾
An already bad marriage got worse
不斷告誡她要相信上帝的存在
Kept telling her to let God in
牧師Boyle 這就解釋的通了
Buddy Boyle,that explains it
解釋了什麼
Explains what
沒什麼
Never mind
這是他的車嗎
Was that his truck
對
Yeah
Cass
Nora 她發燒了
Nora,she's really hot
請給我回電話
Please just call,call back
如果你不回電話
If I don't hear back
我就帶她去醫院了
I'm taking her to the hospital
好吧 Tanya 我們出去走走
Okay,Tanya,we're taking a little walk
你好 Castiel
Hello,Castiel
可悲的小傻瓜
Squalid little dump
怪不得她要哭啊
No wonder she cries
她發燒了而已 Ephraim 她會好的
It's a fever,Ephraim.It'll pass
你記得我的名字呢
You remember my name
我們見面的時候 我還什麼都不是呢
I was just nobody when we met
但是你那時候已經是個傳奇人物了
But you,you were a legend
你以前就來過這裏
You've been here before
我是頭一次來人類的世界
This is my first time
它很
And it's
很令人緊張
It's intense
一開始對人性
You know there is a lot you don't
你肯定有很多不明白的地方
Understand about humanity at first
如果你能停下來
If you just stop
停下
Stop
我不會停下的
I won't stop
直到我把這個星球上所有的痛苦清除乾淨
Until I wash the planet clean of all suffering
讓我來吧
Allow me
別碰她
Don't touch her
你以為我是為她而來的
You think I came for her
不 Castiel
No,Castiel
我為你而來
I came for you
接通惡魔電話需要多久
How long will it take to transfer demonic phone call
別吵 鹿鹿
Can it,moose
Crowley 你也打了電話了
Crowley,you got your call
是啊 是時候了
Yeah,It's time
我說是時候了的時候 才是時候了
It's time when I bloody well say it's time
你好 Abadon
Hello Abadon
Crowley
你最近還好嗎
How in the hell are you
這麼多的痛苦和絕望
So much pain and despair
這麼多聲音
So many voices
乞求著解脫
Begging out for relief
你是怎麼找到我的
How did you find me
因為你避開天使了嗎
Because you are warded
和我找到其他病人的方法一樣
The same way I found all my patients
我只是跟著你痛苦的聲音
I just followed the sound of your pain
你不知道那有多大聲
You have no idea how loud it is
我在幾里之外就能聽到
I can hear you from miles
你真的以為
You really you think
你在這裏做天堂的工作嗎
You are doing heaven's work down here
我知道我是的
I know I am
你錯了
Well,you are wrong
地球有時是個很難生存的地方
Earth can be a hard place
這些人類 他們可以變得更好
These humans,they can get better
他們只是在盡力而為
They are just doing the best they can
這就是你認為你在做的事嗎 Castiel
Is that what you think you are doing,Castiel
盡力而為
The best you can
很抱歉
Well,I'm sorry
但如果這就是著名的Castiel的盡力而為
But if this is the best of the famed Castiel can do
你的處境比我想像的還要狼狽
You are a more urgent case than I thought
我曾經崇拜你
I used to admire you
你失敗的的次數遠超過你成功的次數
You failed more often than you succeeded
但至少你曾經是做大事的
But at least you played big
而現在你在做什麼
Now what are you doing
把頭埋在沙子裏
Burying your head in the sand
在你的族人最需要你的時候
Right when your kind need you most
數量怎麼樣
How are the numbers
你是說靈魂數量嗎
You mean souls
比你預想的要多一倍
I've managed a double on your projections
我是怎麼能  成功的
Now,how did I ever pull off such a feat
你在提前收取靈魂
You are taking souls before their time
取消我的契約
Voiding my contracts
是的
That's right
我正在把它們銷毀掉
I'm taking it all down
一點一點
Brick by brick
已經結束了
It's over
Crowley 官僚主義之王 的日子
The days of Crowley,the king of bureaucrat
已經結束了
Are done
馬上就好了
It'll be over soon
我會把疼痛帶走
I'll take the pain away
我想活著
I want to live
但是以什麼身份呢 Castiel
But as what,Castiel
作為天使
As an angel
還是人類
Or a man
你這個
You
骯髒
Ganky
噁心的
Putrescent
婊子
Skanger
我的效率在你看來可能不值一提
It may look like bean-counting to you
可能缺少技巧
May lack a certain adolescent flair
但我的方法奏效
But my way works
你以為你能控制地獄
You think you can control hell
就以這麼混亂的方式
With chaos alone
不用支持 來自
Without the the support of those
依然忠於我的人
Who are still loyal to me
已經有一周沒人看見你了
No one's seen you in weeks
我最後一次見你的時候
And the last I saw you,Howdy and Doody had you
你正被兩兄弟好好地綁著
Tied up nice and tight
好像 把你變成哈巴狗了
Seems to reason,they've turned you into a kennel dog
感覺怎麼樣啊 Crowley
How does it feel Crowley
當了Winchester的婊子
To be the Winchesters' bitch
聽著你在這兒虛張聲勢 還真是有趣
It's been fun indulging in your bluffs
但是你我都知道 你已經沒有權威了
But we both know you have no real authority left
也沒有籌碼
No leverage
你沒什麼能提供給我的
You have nothing to offer me
你一無所有
You have nothing
你的方法
Your way
遲早會遭到反噬
Will backfire
等死吧
You will burn
我等不及了
I can't wait
Crowley
把埃蘭文給我
Give me the translations
我履行我的合約
I keep my agreements
取得原料
Obtain the ingrdients
心臟 弓 榮光
Heart,bow,grace
等等
blah blah blah
混合 直到有煙從灰燼中升起
Mix until the smoke shall rise from the ashes
將天使驅逐出天堂
Casting the angels from heaven
等等
blah blah blah
哦 不可逆轉
Oh,It's irreversible
什麼
What
這個咒語無法被逆轉
The spell can't be undone
新世界已經降臨
The new world order
我們只能受著了
We're stuck with it
你說你想活著
You say you want to live
但是我能看到 你看不到的
But you can't see what I see
選擇一個人類的生命
By choosing a human life
你已經放棄了
You've already given up
你選擇了死亡
You chose death
不可能
There is no way
Crowley在撒謊
Crowley is lying
不 Dean 這次沒有
No,Dean,not this time
Metetron讓這個咒語經得起
Metetron built the spell to withstand
任何讓其逆轉的嘗試
any attempt to reverse it
無法再把天使放回天堂了
There is no putting the angels back in heaven
結束了
It's done
你會告訴Cass嗎
You gonna tell Cass
很抱歉我反應過度了
I'm sorry I overreacted
我的朋友給了我一個小竅門
My friend gave me a tip
少量的醋氨酚能快速退燒
A low dose of acetaminophen brought the fever right down
沒關係
That's okay
我的約會本來就是個災難
Date was a bust anyway
Steve
你說你反應過度
The part of you that overreacted
是因為你在意
That care so much
正是如此 才讓你如此特別
That's what makes you special
我得掛了
I got to go
準備去哪兒啊 Cass
Where to,Cass
聽著 Cass 在基地裏
Listen Cass,back at the bunker
我 很抱歉我把你趕走了
I...Sorry I told to go
我知道你過得很不容易
I know it's been hard on you
你只剩自己一個人
You know,on your own
但你適應了
The way you are adapting
我為你驕傲
I'm proud of you
謝謝你 Dean
Thank you,Dean
但是就像Ephraim說的
But there is something Ephraim said
天使們 他們需要幫助
The angels,they need help
難道我真的能坐視不理
Can I really sit this out
難道我不該尋找讓他們回家的途徑嗎
Shouldn't I be searching for a way to get them home
我和Sam會處理天使的事
Me and Sam will take care of the angels
你現在是人類了
You are human now
這不再是你的問題了
It's not your problem anymore
流星雨已經過去幾周了
It's been weeks since the massive meteor storm
但是愛達荷州的天文學家
Yet Idaho falls astronomers still
還沒有給出答覆
Have unanswered questions
華盛頓當局和航天局
NASA and Washington are both continuing
將繼續研究這一現象
To study the phenomenon